<div style="font-family:Arial; font-size:10pt; margin-left: 20px;  margin-top: 10px; margin-bottom:20px; margin-right:0px;">
Legal Name: [[LEGAL_NAME]]<br>
Provider NPI: [[NPI]]<br>
Issue Date: [[CURRENTDATE]] <br>
<p>The MAXIMUS Enrollment Specialist has approved all screening for the above Group Provider but the provider has requested an effective date for a Group Member that is more than 6 months prior to their enrollment receipt date.  </p>
<p>Program Integrity will need to review this provider to determine if the retro effective date can be accepted per District of Columbia Medicaid policy.  </p>
<p>Below are the Group Member(s) where retro effective dates have been requested:<br />
[[MemberDetails]]</p>
<p>Please log into the Screening and Enrollment portal to complete a review of this provider and take the next appropriate action.<br />
[[PDMSURL]]</p>
<p>Regards,<br>
MAXIMUS Provider Screening and Enrollment Customer Service
</p>
</div>
