<div style="font-family:Arial; font-size:10pt; margin-left: 20px;  margin-top: 10px; margin-bottom:20px; margin-right:0px;">
Legal Name: [[LEGAL_NAME]]<br>
Provider NPI: [[NPI]]<br>
Issue Date: [[CURRENTDATE]] <br>
<p>The MAXIMUS Enrollment Specialist has approved all screening for the above Provider but the provider has requested an effective date that is prior to their enrollment receipt date.  </p>
<p>Program Integrity will need to review this provider to determine if the retro effective date can be accepted per (State) Medicaid policy.  </p>
<p>Below are the important dates you will need to consider when making your decision:</p>
Requested Effective Date: [[REQUESTED_EFFECTIVE_DATE]]<br>
Enrollment Receipt Date: [[SUBMIT_DATE_TIME]]<br>

<p>Please log into the Screening and Enrollment portal to complete a review of this provider and take the next appropriate action.<br />
[[PDMSURL]]</p>
<p>Regards,<br>
MAXIMUS Provider Screening and Enrollment Customer Service
</p>
</div>
